const quizData = [
	{
		question:
			"What tag is used to define a container for an external app or plug-in",
		answers: ["<caption>", "<!DOCTYPE>", "<code>", "<embed>"],
	},
	{
		question: "What tag is used to define a standard cell inside a table",
		answers: ["<h1> to <h6>", "<td>", "<button>", "<footer>"],
	},
	{
		question: "What tag is used to define a hyperlink, or link to another page",
		answers: ["<a>", "<em>", "<strong>", "<blockquote>"],
	},
	{
		question: "What tag is used to define a list item (in a bulleted list)",
		answers: ["<s>", "<ul>", "<u>", "<li>"],
	},
	{
		question:
			"What tag is used to define an interactive field where users can enter data?",
		answers: ["<dialog>", "<enterpoint>", "<datalist>", "<input>"],
	},
	{
		question:
			"What element is a container for all the head elements, and may include the document title, scripts, styles, meta information, and more?",
		answers: ["<head></head>", "<br></br>", "<body></body>", "<title></title>"],
	},
	{
		question:
			"What tag is used to specify a section of text that provides an example of computer code?",
		answers: ["<embed>", "<code>", "<caption>", "<!DOCTYPE>"],
	},
	{
		question:
			"What tag is used to specify a section of text that has been quoted from another source?",
		answers: ["<em>", "<strong>", "<blockquote>", "<a>"],
	},
	{
		question:
			"What tag can be used to insert a line break or blank line in an HTML document?",
		answers: ["<br></br>", "<body></body>", "<head></head>", "<title></title>"],
	},

	{
		question: "What tag is used to define a table or image notation (caption)?",
		answers: ["<caption>", "<code>", "<embed>", "<!DOCTYPE>"],
	},
];

export default quizData;
